A Guide to the Edgar B. Young papers FA109
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Lincoln Center, Inc., 1952-1980 (1956-1976); 1956-1976; 1; 26.48 Cubic Feet 68 letter document boxes, 1 legal document box, and 1 flat file folder; 69 Boxes 27.6 cubic feet
  - Planning and Construction, 1956-1978; 9
    - Juilliard Building - Acoustics - Practice Room, 1965-September 1969 (1970) (Box 44, Folder 552)
    - Juilliard Building - Acoustics - Practice Room, October 1969-January 1972 (1970) (Box 44, Folder 553)
    - Juilliard Building - Alice Tully Hall (Chamber Music Recital Hall) - Acoustics - Bolt, Beranek and Newman Studios, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 554)
    - Juilliard Building - Alice Tully Hall (Chamber Music Recital Hall) - General Files, 1959-April 1963 (1971) (Box 44, Folder 555)
    - Juilliard Building - Alice Tully Hall (Chamber Music Recital Hall) - General Files, August 1963-February 1966 (1971) (Box 44, Folder 556)
    - Juilliard Building - Alice Tully Hall (Chamber Music Recital Hall) - General Files, May 1966-March 1969 (1971) (Box 44, Folder 557)
    - Juilliard Building - Alice Tully Hall (Chamber Music Recital Hall) - General Files, April 1969-1970 (1971) (Box 44, Folder 558)
    - Juilliard Building - America-Israel Music Alliance, 1963-1964 (1971) (Box 44, Folder 559)
    - photocopy of Julliard School of Music site plan, with correspondence, 1964 May 8; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 4)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction, Box 44, Folder 559
    - Juilliard Building - Buildings, 1963-1968 (1971) (Box 45, Folder 560)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 12. Architectural material has been removed and is housed separately.
    - photocopy of Julliard School of Music site plan, with correspondence, 1964 May 8; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 4)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction, Box 45, Folder 560
    - photocopy of Amsterdam Tower plan, Julliard School of Music, with correspondence, 1964 June 1; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 4)
    - photocopy of Julliard School of Music floor plans, with correspondence, 1964 June 1; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 4)
    - Juilliard Building - Completion of the Building, 1969-April 1970 (1971) (Box 45, Folder 561)
    - Juilliard Building - Completion of the Building, June 1970-February 4, 1971 (1971) (Box 45, Folder 562)
    - Juilliard Building - Completion of the Building, February 24, 1971 (1971) (Box 45, Folder 563)
    - Juilliard Building - Completion of the Building, February 26-May 1971 (1971) (Box 45, Folder 564)
    - Juilliard Building - Completion of the Building, June 1970-February 1972 (1971) (Box 45, Folder 565)
    - Juilliard Building - Construction, 1962-1965 (1970) (Box 45, Folder 566)
    - Juilliard Building - Construction, 1966 (1970) (Box 45, Folder 567)
    - Juilliard Building - Construction, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 568)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 13.
    - Juilliard Building - Construction, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 569)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2037
    - Juilliard Building - Construction, 1968-1971 (1970) (Box 45, Folder 570)
    - Juilliard Building - Dormitory Planning, 1957-1972 (1971) (Box 46, Folder 571)
    - Juilliard Building - Furniture and Fixtures, 1968-June 1969 (1971) (Box 46, Folder 572)
    - Juilliard Building - Furniture and Fixtures, July 1969-April 24, 1970 (1971) (Box 46, Folder 573)
    - Juilliard Building - Furniture and Fixtures, April 28, 1970 (1971) (Box 46, Folder 574)
    - Juilliard Building - Furniture and Fixtures, April 29-September 16, 1970 (1971) (Box 46, Folder 575)
    - Juilliard Building - Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project - General Files, circa1964-April 15, 1965 (1970) (Box 46, Folder 576)
    - photocopy of street plan of Julliard Building, Lincoln Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project, 1965 April 15; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 5)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction Box 46, Folder 576
    - map of "Lincoln Square Area" from Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project General Files, 1965 April 15; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 5)
    - Juilliard Building - Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project - General Files, April 20-September 30, 1965 (1970) (Box 46, Folder 577)
    - Juilliard Building - Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project - General Files, November-December 1965 (1970) (Box 46, Folder 578)
    - Juilliard Building - Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project - General Files, 1966 (1970) (Box 46, Folder 579)
    - Juilliard Building - Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project - General Files, 1967-1972 (1970) (Box 46, Folder 580)
    - Juilliard Building - Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project - High School of Commerce Site (LaGuardia High School of Music and the Arts), 1962-1971 (Box 46, Folder 581)
    - Juilliard Building - Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project - High School of Commerce Site (LaGuardia High School of Music and the Arts), 1972 (Box 46, Folder 582)
    - Juilliard Building - Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project - High School of Commerce Site (LaGuardia High School of Music and the Arts), 1973-March 1974 (Box 46, Folder 583)
    - Juilliard Building - Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project - High School of Commerce Site (LaGuardia High School of Music and the Arts), December 1974-1978 (Box 47, Folder 584)
    - set of 6 drawings "Feasibility Study for Lincoln Center of Proposed Multi-Use Building... " Schemes 1-4B, 1974 December-1968; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 6) (Drawer D 14, Folder 5)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction Box 47, Folder 584
    - Juilliard Building - Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project - High School of Music and Art; High School of Performing Arts, 1958-1960 (Box 47, Folder 585)
    - Juilliard Building - Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project - High School of Music and Art; High School of Performing Arts, 1961 (Box 47, Folder 586)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 14.
    - Juilliard Building - Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project - High School of Music and Art; High School of Performing Arts, 1962-1970 (Box 47, Folder 587)
    - Juilliard Building - Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project - High School of Music and Art; High School of Performing Arts, 1971-1972 (Box 47, Folder 588)
    - Juilliard Building - Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project - New York City Agreement, 1966 February 1 (Box 47, Folder 589)
      Copy.
    - Juilliard Building - Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project - Title I, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 590)
    - Juilliard Building - Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project - Title I, February-May 1963 (Box 47, Folder 591)
    - Juilliard Building - Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project - Title I, June-December 1963 (Box 47, Folder 592)
    - Juilliard Building - Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project - Title I, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 593)
    - Juilliard Building - Millwork, 1965-1968 (Box 47, Folder 594)
    - Juilliard Building - New York State Urban Development Corporation (UDC), 1971-1973 (Box 47, Folder 595)
    - Juilliard Building - Planning - Final, 1961-June 1963 (Box 47, Folder 596)
    - Juilliard Building - Planning - Final, 1963-1964 (Box 47, Folder 597)
    - Juilliard Building - Planning - Final, 1964 September-1965 January (Box 48, Folder 598)
    - Juilliard Building - Planning - Final, February 1965-1966 (Box 48, Folder 599)
    - Juilliard Building - Planning - Final, 1967-1970 (Box 48, Folder 600)
    - Julliard School of Music site plan for green space, photocopy w/ correspondence, 1967-1970; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 5)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction Box 48, Folder 600
    - Juilliard Building - Planning - Preliminary, 1957-1960 (Box 48, Folder 601)
    - Juilliard Building - Planning - Preliminary, 1961-1964 (Box 48, Folder 602)
    - Juilliard Building - Site Expansion, January-February 1958 (Box 48, Folder 603)
    - photocopy of site and street plans of Lincoln Center, w/ correspondence, 1958 January-February; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 5)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction, Box 48, Folder 603
    - Julliard Building site expansion, 1958 January-February; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 5)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction Box 48, Folder 603
    - Juilliard Building - Site Expansion, March 1958 (Box 48, Folder 604)
    - Juilliard Building - Site Expansion, April-November 1958 (Box 48, Folder 605)
    - Juilliard Building - Site Expansion, 1961-1964 (Box 48, Folder 606)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 15.
    - Juilliard Building - Stage Equipment and Lighting - Brake Noise in Winches, 1969 December-1970 April (Box 48, Folder 607)
    - Juilliard Building - Stage Equipment and Lighting - Brake Noise in Winches, 1970 May-1971 March (Box 48, Folder 608)
    - Juilliard Building - Stage Equipment and Lighting - General Files, 1965 September-1966 September (Box 48, Folder 609)
    - Juilliard Building - Stage Equipment and Lighting - General Files, 1966 October-1967 May (Box 48, Folder 610)
    - Juilliard Building - Stage Equipment and Lighting - General Files, 1968 July-December (Box 48, Folder 611)
    - Juilliard Building - Stage Equipment and Lighting - General Files, 1969-1970 (Box 48, Folder 612)
    - Juilliard Building - Title II Grant, 1965-1967 (Box 49, Folder 613)
    - Juilliard Building - Window Cleaning Scaffold, 1968-1970 (Box 49, Folder 614)
    - Juilliard Building - Window Cleaning Scaffold, 1971-July 1972 (Box 49, Folder 615)
    - Juilliard Building - Window Cleaning Scaffold, September-December 1972 (Box 49, Folder 616)
    - Kennedy Building, April 1957-October 1959 (Box 49, Folder 617)
    - Kennedy Building, November 1959-June 1961 (Box 49, Folder 618)
    - Labor Advisory Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 49, Folder 619)
    - Labor Advisory Committee, 1960-March 1961 (Box 49, Folder 620)
    - Labor Advisory Committee, April 1961-June 1963 (Box 49, Folder 621)
    - Labor Advisory Committee, July 1963-1969 (Box 49, Folder 622)
    - Library/Museum Furniture, Sound Equipment, etc., 1962-1965 (Box 49, Folder 623)
    - Library/Museum and New York State Theater - Negotiations with New York City and New York State - Agreement, January 8, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 624)
    - Repertory Theatre for Drama and Library Museum, Lincoln Center, 1964 January 6; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 9) (Drawer D 14, Folder 7)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction Box 49, Folder 624
    - Library/Museum and New York State Theater - Negotiations with New York City and New York State - General Files, July 1957-January 1959 (Box 49, Folder 625)
    - Library/Museum and New York State Theater - Negotiations with New York City and New York State - General Files, 1959 February-March 17 (Box 49, Folder 626)
    - Library/Museum and New York State Theater - Negotiations with New York City and New York State - General Files, 1959 March 21-1960 June (Box 50, Folder 627)
    - Library/Museum and New York State Theater - Negotiations with New York City and New York State - General Files, 1960 September-1961 January 13 (Box 50, Folder 628)
    - Library/Museum and New York State Theater - Negotiations with New York City and New York State - General Files, 1961 January 17-March 18 (Box 50, Folder 629)
    - Library/Museum and New York State Theater - Negotiations with New York City and New York State - General Files, 1961 March 20-April (Box 50, Folder 630)
    - Library/Museum and New York State Theater - Negotiations with New York City and New York State - General Files, 1964-1966 (Box 50, Folder 631)
    - Library/Museum and New York State Theater - Negotiations with New York City and New York State - General Files, 1961 May-November (Box 50, Folder 632)
    - Library/Museum and New York State Theater - Negotiations with New York City and New York State - General Files, 1961 November 28- 1962 February (Box 50, Folder 633)
    - Library/Museum and New York State Theater - Negotiations with New York City and New York State - General Files, 1962 March-June (Box 50, Folder 634)
    - Library/Museum and New York State Theater - Negotiations with New York City and New York State - General Files, 1962 August-1963 July (Box 50, Folder 635)
    - Library/Museum and New York State Theater - Negotiations with New York City and New York State - General Files, August 1963-April 1964 (Box 50, Folder 636)
    - Library/Museum and New York State Theater - Negotiations with New York City and New York State - General Files, July 1964-1965 (Box 50, Folder 637)
    - Library/Museum and New York State Theater - Negotiations with New York City and New York State - General Files, March 1966-October 1967 (Box 50, Folder 638)
    - Lincoln Center Plaza - General Files, 1962-1964 (Box 50, Folder 639)
    - Lincoln Center Plaza - General Files, 1965-1968 (Box 51, Folder 640)
    - Lincoln Square Urban Renewal Project - History of Land Offers, 1957-1959 (Box 51, Folder 641)
    - Lincoln Square Urban Renewal Project - Reports, Committee on Slum Clearance, City Planning Commission, 1956-January 1957 (Box 51, Folder 642)
    - Lincoln Square Urban Renewal Project - Reports, Committee on Slum Clearance, City Planning Commission, July 1957-1958 (Box 51, Folder 643)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Acoustics - Bolt, Beranek and Newman Studies - General, 1959; 1961 (Box 51, Folder 644)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Acoustics - Bolt, Beranek and Newman Studies - Report No. 693 - pp. 1-50, 1959 December 15 (Box 51, Folder 645)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Acoustics - Bolt, Beranek and Newman Studies - Report No. 693 - pp. 51-100, 1959 December 15 (Box 51, Folder 646)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Acoustics - Bolt, Beranek and Newman Studies - Report No. 693 - pp. 101-end, 1959 December 15 (Box 51, Folder 647)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Chandeliers (Austrian Gift), May-July 1963 (Box 51, Folder 648)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Chandeliers (Austrian Gift), April-August 1964 (Box 51, Folder 649)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 16.
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Chandeliers (Austrian Gift), October 1964-May 1965 (Box 51, Folder 650)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Chandeliers (Austrian Gift), 1965 June-September 16 (Box 51, Folder 651)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Chandeliers (Austrian Gift), 1965 September 17-December (Box 51, Folder 652)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Chandeliers (Austrian Gift), January-June 1966 (Box 51, Folder 653)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Chandeliers (Austrian Gift), July 1966-February 1967 (Box 52, Folder 654)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Chandeliers (Austrian Gift), March 1967-June 1968 (Box 52, Folder 655)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Costs and Budgets, March 1961-1963 (Box 52, Folder 656)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Costs and Budgets, 1964 (1971) (Box 52, Folder 657)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Costs and Budgets, February-July 1965 (1971) (Box 52, Folder 658)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Costs and Budgets, August-December 1965 (1971) (Box 52, Folder 659)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Costs and Budgets, February-April 22, 1966 (1971) (Box 52, Folder 660)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Costs and Budgets, April 25-May 12, 1966 (1971) (Box 52, Folder 661)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Costs and Budgets, July-November 14, 1966 (1971) (Box 52, Folder 662)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Costs and Budgets, 1966 November 21-1969 January 14 (Box 52, Folder 663)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - General Files, July 1958-July 1962 (Box 52, Folder 664)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - General Files, October 1962-1963 November 11 (Box 52, Folder 665)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - General Files, 1963 November 20-1964 December (Box 52, Folder 666)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 17.
    - Metropolitan Opera House - General Files, 1965-January 1966 (1971) (Box 52, Folder 667)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - General Files, April 1966-June 1967 (1971) (Box 52, Folder 668)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - General Files, September 1967-December 1968 (1971) (Box 53, Folder 669)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Harrison & Abramovitz Meetings Minutes, 1957-1960 (Box 53, Folder 670)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Opening - General Files, January-July 1966 (1971) (Box 53, Folder 671)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Opening - General Files, 1961-1965 (1975) (Box 53, Folder 672)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Opening - General Files, August-September 1966 (1971) (Box 53, Folder 673)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Patron Plaques and Founders Hall, 1964-1971 (1971); 1972 (Box 53, Folder 674)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Restaurants, 1961-1966 (1971) (Box 53, Folder 675)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - "Save the Met", 1966-1967 (1971) (Box 53, Folder 676)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Stage Equipment, 1963-1966 November 21 (Box 53, Folder 677)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Stage Equipment, February 1967 (1971) (Box 53, Folder 678)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Stage Equipment, March-November 1967 (1971) (Box 53, Folder 679)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Stage Equipment, 1968 (1971) (Box 53, Folder 680)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Television, 1961-1967 (1971) (Box 53, Folder 681)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Traffic, 1963-1966 (1971) (Box 53, Folder 682)
    - New York City - Contract - Agreement, December 10, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 683)
    - New York City - Contract - Agreement, August 21, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 684)
      Includes Supplemental Agreement.
    - New York City - Contract - Agreement, January 14, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 685)
    - New York City - Contract - Draft, August-September 1957 (Box 54, Folder 686)
    - New York City - Department of Parks, April 1960-October 1964 (1971) (Box 54, Folder 687)
    - New York City - Department of Parks, November 1964-September 1965 (1971) (Box 54, Folder 688)
    - Re-Development of Lincoln Center Square Park, photocopy w/ correspondence, 1960 May 5; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 6)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction Box 54, Folder 688
    - Study for Development of Triangular Park Area, photocopy, w/ correspondence, 1964 November-1965 September; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 6)
    - Existing Condition of Broadway Malls, with correspondence., 1964 November-1965 September; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 6)
    - New York City - Department of Parks, October-December 1965 (1971) (Box 54, Folder 689)
    - New York City - Department of Parks, 1966 (1971) (Box 54, Folder 690)
    - New York City - Department of Parks, February 1967-1970 (1971) (Box 54, Folder 691)
    - Lincoln Center site, photocopy w/correspondence, 1955 March; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 6)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction Box 54, Folder 691
    - New York City - Financing, 1967-1969 (Box 54, Folder 692)
    - New York City - Miscellany, 1961-1967 (Box 54, Folder 693)
    - New York City - Public Relations, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 694)
    - New York State Theater - Agreements (Architectural and Construction), 1962 (1971) (Box 54, Folder 695)
    - New York State Theater - General Files, September 1961-March 1964 (1971) (Box 54, Folder 696)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 18.
    - New York State Theater - Construction, 1958-July 1961 (1971) (Box 55, Folder 697)
    - New York State Theater - Construction, August 1964-March 1965 (1971) (Box 55, Folder 698)
    - New York State Theater - Construction, November 1965-1968 (1971) (Box 55, Folder 699)
    - New York State Theater - Cornerstone and Plaque, 1962-1963 (1971) (Box 55, Folder 700)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 19.
    - New York State Theater - Cornerstone and Plaque, 1964 (1971) (Box 55, Folder 701)
    - New York State Theater - Negotiations with New York State - Agreement, December 1962 (1971) (Box 55, Folder 702)
    - New York State Theater - Negotiations with New York State - General Files, 1957-March 1961 (1971) (Box 55, Folder 703)
    - New York State Theater - Negotiations with New York State - General Files, April 1961-1965 (1971) (Box 55, Folder 704)
    - New York State Theater - Office Space, 1963-1965 (1971) (Box 55, Folder 705)
    - New York State Theater - Opening Night - General Files, 1963 (1971) (Box 55, Folder 706)
    - New York State Theater - Opening Night - General Files, 1964 (1971) (Box 55, Folder 707)
    - New York State Theater - Opening Night - Invitations, February-March 17, 1964 (1971) (Box 55, Folder 708)
    - New York State Theater - Opening Night - Invitations, March 19, 1964-1971 (1971) (Box 55, Folder 709)
    - New York State Theater - Opening Week, 1962-January 1964 (1971) (Box 56, Folder 710)
    - New York State Theater - Opening Week, January 28-March 20, 1964 (1971) (Box 56, Folder 711)
    - New York State Theater - Opening Week, March 26-May 1964 (1971) (Box 56, Folder 712)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Acoustics - Avery Fisher Hall, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 713)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Acoustics - Bolt, Beranek and Newman Studies, 1958-July 1959 (Box 56, Folder 714)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Acoustics - Bolt, Beranek and Newman Studies, October 1959-April 1960 (Box 56, Folder 715)
    - Comparison of March 1959 Plan with September 1959 Plan-Philharmonic Plan, Lincoln Center, with correspondence, 1959 October 28; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 6)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction Box 56, Folder 715
    - Philharmonic Hall Acoustics Study, Lincoln Center w/ correspondence, WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 6)
    - comparison of Philharmonic, Carnegie, Boston, and Grosser music halls, 1962 November-1963 June; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 7)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning and Construction, Box 56, Folder 715
    - Family of Halls, comparisons, 1962 November-1963 June; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 7)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Acoustics - Bolt, Beranek and Newman Studies, November 1962; June 1963 (Box 56, Folder 716)
    - Family of Halls with Similar Ceiling Shapes, 1962 November-1963 June; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 7)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning and Construction, Box 56, Folder 716
    - Philharmonic Hall - Acoustics - General Files, undated (Box 56, Folder 717)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Acoustics - General Files, 1959; 1962 (Box 56, Folder 718)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 20.
    - Philharmonic Hall - Acoustics - General Files, 1963-1964 (Box 56, Folder 719)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Acoustics - General Files, 1965-1969 (Box 56, Folder 720)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Acoustics - General Files, 1976-1977 (Box 56, Folder 721)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Acoustics - Phases I and II, 1962-1963 (1971) (Box 56, Folder 722)
      Includes Philharmonic Hall seating chart, April 1963.
    - Philharmonic Hall - Acoustics - Phase III, February-July 8, 1964 (1971) (Box 56, Folder 723)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Acoustics - Phase IV, April-June 1965 (1971) (Box 56, Folder 724)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Acoustics - Phase IV, July-September 20, 1965 (1971) (Box 57, Folder 725)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Acoustics - Phase IV, September 22, 1965-1970 (1971) (Box 57, Folder 726)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Acoustics - Phase V - "1969 Project - Philharmonic Hall", 1967-1969 (1971) (Box 57, Folder 727)